GRADE 2 CLASS 2
PLAY
ALADDIN, MOMOTARO, OPERA, ALICE
GRADE 2 CLASS 2, CLASS REPRESENTATIVES
EXCITED
WHOA...
OH...
HOMEROOM TEACHER
SMILE
WAVE WAVE
LOOKS AWAY
EPISODE 16
STOP AND GO
MEITEN HIGH SCHOOL BAND
OPEN 17: 00
RUMBLE RUMBLE RUMBLE
CONVENTIONAL LINE (EAST EXIT GATES)
SUBWAY (WEST EXIT GATES)
MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH
SO PEACEFUL...
SMIRK...
THUD
GASP
STAND UP
PUNCH PUNCH PUNCH
NUDGE NUDGE
SNAP
GRIN
HEH
HEH HEH
LOOKS AWAY
TWITCH
RUMBLE RUMBLE RUMBLE
PREPARING FOR THE CULTURAL FESTIVAL
LOVE LOVE LOVE LOVE
I LIKE YOU
DIFFERENT KINDS
THE SIZES ARE DIFFERENT
I'M THE ONLY ONE STRUGGLING
MEITEN HIGH SCHOOL
SUMMER BREAK
CAST MEMBERS REHEARSING
STARE...
LAMP (TEMPORARY)
MEITEN HIGH SCHOOL